You know your way around a sword.
I'll grant you that much,
but it will take much more
than mere ego if you think
I'll be defeated by the time
the flames reach twelve.
Your pride may well be your
undoing, mister...uh...who?
Pardonnez-moi.
We haven't been introduced yet.
My name is Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
Well met, Polnareff.
It's good to know the
name of one's opponent.
However...
Back to the task at hand.
If you're under the
assumption that my flames only
burn upward or with the wind
as they would in nature,
let me assure you they do not.
My stand is named Magician's Red because
it wields fire as though by magic.
Fire is what began life
itself in this world.
I should have expected as much from
a fiery stand such as Magician's Red,
who represents beginnings.
However, you dare to
speak of pride and ego?
I assure you that my
pride is well deserved!
In the fraction of a second
that the coins lined up,
he skewered all five of them
in a single shot! No. Huh?
Why don't you take a look at him again?
It can't be.
There, stuck on the blade of his sword.
He's cut a bit of flame
for every coin that he hit.
Now you see that I'm every
bit as deadly as I had said.
This is not mere ego.
My stand has the unrestricted power to cut
fire to ribbons as though it were nothing.
It can slice through air, creating
a vacuum and guiding the fire.
Your flames are useless.
Face it,
your magician's red may be fearsome,
but it's powerless against the
likes of my silver chariot!
How the devil?
Victory and conquest.
That represents the card, the
chariot, and defines my stand as well.
I can beat you in this cramped little
place as well as anywhere else.
Not very sporting, though.
Your flames will serve you to greater
effect in a larger open space.
Beating you at the apex
of your powers, Monsieur,
is the only victory worthy of my stand.
All of you, follow me outside!
Thank you
so
much for watching.
Thank you.
What the hell kind of nonsense is this?
I believe they call it
Tiger Balm Garden. Oh, yeah?
Tiger Balm Garden,
a fantastical hillside park built
along Hong Kong's famous Tai Han Road.
With its surreal landscape of sculptures
and pagodas, it is a true Hong Kong oddity.
A prediction, if I may indulge.
Monsieur Avdol, you will die here.
Destroyed by the flames of your
very own stand, Magician's Red.
Avdol, Jotaro, this is not your fight.
In an open space like this one, there's
nothing to keep my stand from fighting.
at full force.
En Card!
Nothing at all?
No sign of the flame you
were crying about before?
Suit yourself!
I shall press the attack!
That goddamn bastard,
he's just toying with us!
He used Magician's Reds on
fireballs to make a statue of it!
Look at that!
In a place this odd, I dare say
your fiendish face is right at home.
Well, here it comes.
Show me your true power at last, Avdol,
but know that it will never be enough.
Hey, hide behind something already.
Avdol's gonna blow his top.
What are you talking about?
Crossfire!
Rock!
Really?
Is that the best that you've got?
I told you before what my sword does.
It creates a gap between the pockets
of air so I can slice your flames!
Abdel, no!
The fire is so intense, it's
burning Stan and user alike!
It's just as I foretold.
You will die from an inferno
of your own making. Hmm?
Good grief, just die already.
One last pathetic gasp,
this is hard to watch.
That hit felt wrong, what is this?
What?
Impossible.
How can his stand injure me after
the moment of its own destruction?
It's not the stand, you
bastard, it's a dummy.
The flames blinded your eyes.
What you really destroyed was the statue
that Silver Chariot carved earlier!
Perhaps you didn't take
me at my word when I
told you that I could
control my flames freely.
When you deflected it, I used it to melt
the statue's joints and allow it to move.
The one defeated by his own
stance powers is you, Polnareff!
Now, let's try this again!
Crossfire Hurricane! SHINE!
Challenging a fortune-teller in a
battle of predictions is a bold move.
Give it another decade and you
would have been a viable opponent.
Such terrifying power!
His stand must have melted in
the face of such an attack!
It's done for!
That's one hell of a burn.
I'm betting he's dead.
Or wishes he was.
Yeah, he's not getting up from that.
If he is alive, he'll be
flat on his back for months.
Having your stand destroyed
is a major trauma.
Now then, Mr.
Joestar, let us resume
our trek to Egypt. Hmm.
What the hell's going on?
His stand just exploded
into a bunch of pieces!
How is he still lying down
but suspended in midair?
Bravo!
Well done, Monsieur Bravo!
That's impossible!
I don't believe it!
He doesn't look injured at all! Yeah!
But Why the hell is he
floating in the air?
Look with your inner
eye and see the truth!
How can it be?
Out of control.
Me well, monsieur.
He may have shed his armor, but
it's still my silver chariot.
You seem quite taken aback by this.
I really should explain
before I destroy you.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be
chivalrous, don't you agree?
I'm sure you were expecting
nothing less, if you don't mind.
May we take a short time
out for an explanation? Hmm.
Very well.
Let's hear this explanation.
First, the explosion you saw was
not my stand self-destructing.
What you took as Silver
Chariot's body was armor.
Armor that was cast off.
But before it did, it absorbed
the brunt of your flames.
That's how I escaped further harm.
And bereft of armor, it has
significantly more agility.
Were you able to see my
stand as it held me up?
That's right.
Silver Chariot can now
move faster than before.
Hmm.
Illuminating.
You're suggesting it only stood
there and took my crossfire
hurricane head-on because the
armor didn't allow it to dodge,
is that it?
But bereft of armor, it is
also far more vulnerable.
It may have survived
my attack once before,
but if it were hit again, its
destruction would be absolute.
That may be.
Whee!
How can one know?
Such a shame, we'll never find out.
Never, huh?
Well, mind if I try it out?
First, let me show you all something
that will really freak you out.
Well, go ahead then.
What the devil?
He now has six, no, no wait, he
has a total of seven stands now.
But that's impossible.
There should only be one stand per user.
Tell me, are you freaked out yet?
These are after images.
Perfect mirrors of the Silver Chariot,
Guaranteed to fool your senses.
Your sight, your hearing, your senses
can't follow their movement. Ugh.
How do you like
insultsmanship now, monsieur?
Suffer my red bun!
Ah!
I told you that efforts to track
it would be in vain, did I not?
You waste your flame on images
and spare the real threat.
Striking at random.
Desperation is not a good
look on you, my dear Abdo.
He's going to exhaust
himself at this rate.
Crossfire!
Hurricane!
Menon, menon, menon, menon, menon!
Have you learned nothing at all today?
You're a fool whose attacks will
not work on my stand! Now give up!
Haptor!
What precision, what lethal
efficiency, it's plain to see.
His stand's ability has been
trained, and at great length!
Hmm, I've spent the last
decade honing my skill.
You had better hit me with
everything you've got,
for I intend my next attack
to be the coup de grace.
It's very chivalrous of you to keep giving
me fair warning about your next move.
Your honor is unimpeachable.
You've inspired me, thus I too will
give fair warning before my next attack.
Really?
varieties than the one
you've already seen.
It's a flame in the shape of an
ankh but it need not remain whole.
I can divide it into as
many pieces as I deem fit.
Crossfire Hurricane Special!
Try and dodge them!
You're a fool, Abdaal, it's useless!
Damn, they've got him covered!
He's thought of everything!
Naive, naive, naive!
So very naive!
I will wield this divided flame
against you precisely as I did before!
Slice it!
And hurl it back!
What?!
That's...
that's the hole that was
dug by the flames earlier.
Now I get it! It's clear to me!
The first shot was a
setup and nothing more!
Then he used the tunnel to hit
him with Crossfire Hurricane!
Like I said, that attack can be divided
up into as many pieces as are called for.
Burning is a painful
way to meet one's end.
Take the knife and end it while you can.
My conceit was my undoing.
I couldn't picture his fire standing
a chance against my sword work.
A slow death amid the flames is
no less than I deserve, monsieur.
I challenged you to this duel
and you were the clear victor.
I would not sully it with suicide.
It would be cowardly to end it myself.
Even in your final moments, you
conduct yourself with chivalry.
How easy it would have been for you to
throw that knife into my unsuspecting back.
Even while working for a devil like
Dio, you've carried yourself with honor.
Your death would be a waste.
Hmm?
Something must have set
him down this dark path.
Jojo.
Gotcha.
Those tentacles are so gross,
I can't even look at them!
Come on, Jotaro!
Just destroy the damn thing!
Quit your bitchin', old man!
There!
Now that my grandson has pulled out
that flesh, bud, we can all be buddies!
You get it?
Hey, Kakuline.
Don't people who make stupid puns all the
time get on your nerves, or is it just me?
The Speedwagon Foundation
chartered a boat for us yesterday.
With any luck, it's reached
the harbor ahead of us.
We meet again.
So what's on your mind, Polnareff?
I never thanked you properly for
freeing me from Dio's mind control.
Young Jojo is the one you
should be thanking here.
Don't need your thanks.
It appears your fine manners
are wasted on the likes of us.
As you wish, I've no desire
to come off as heavy-handed.
But I'm not quite finished here.
Monsieur Joestar, I hope you'll indulge
my asking a very bizarre question.
A bizarre question, you say?
I noticed at the restaurant
yesterday that you
never took off your
gloves even while eating.
Tell me, your left hand wouldn't happen
to be a right hand under that glove?
Huh?
Is my left hand a right one?
You weren't kidding
about the bizarre part.
What are you hoping to
find out through all this?
I'm looking for the man who
murdered my younger sister.
I don't know his face, but he definitely
has two right hands instead of one of each.
Here I lost a real thing in a
horrible battle some 50 years ago.
I apologize for the rudeness.
Please forgive me if it's not
too painful to talk about.
I'd like to know what happened.
It's
been
three years now.
My younger sister and a classmate of hers
were walking home from school in the rain,
back in our native France.
It was a country road,
much like any other.
On the side of the road, a man
stood with his back to them.
Oddly enough, the
mysterious stranger was dry.
The rain fell in torrents around him, as
though an invisible shell guarded him.
Suddenly,
her friend fell to the
ground in a fountain of
blood as though her chest
was cut by the wind.
My sister was alone.
He stole her innocence
and then he killed her.
That was all the man wanted.
For that she died.
Her friend escaped with her life to
tell me what she saw that fateful day.
She didn't get a good look
at their tormentors face.
But saw that both of his
hands were right hands.
No one believed the poor
girl's testimony about the man.
No one but me. That is.
I had already been keeping my own
strange powers a secret by then.
And he sounded like a fellow stand user.
He's a stand user all right.
I'm sure of it.
I swore an oath.
I promised my sister's soul that I would
avenge her to hunt down the killer.
and make him pay with his life!
I would use my own stand as a
tool of righteous vengeance!
Then, a year ago, my
travels led me to Dio.
That... man!
The reflection shows.
It's a vision from your heart, not mine.
The man you seek, the pain you hide.
My power only makes it visible.
How about it, Polnareff?
Care to become friends?
Tragedy gnaws away at your soul.
I need no glass to see that.
Work with me and your suffering will soon
be nothing more than a thing of the past.
The image in the globe is
what pains you, is it not?
What if I could help you?
I too am plagued with misfortune.
I have been denied the
sun's embrace forevermore.
Be an agent of my will out in the sunlight
and I will find this
man who haunts you so.
After that, I was commanded
to kill all four of you.
Never once did I question my orders.
Even if he hadn't used a flesh bud,
Dio is quite the master at manipulating
human beings to carry out his bidding.
Truly.
And if Dio has found your sister's killer,
we might safely assume he's enlisted the
villain in whatever dark
plans he's got afoot.
If that is true, I must join you
on your trek to Egypt, messieurs.
By going after Dio, I will find
the one who took my sister's life.
What do we do?
I have no objections to him coming.
Even if we tell him no, I'm
sure he'll just follow along.
Jean-Pierre Polnirath.
Stand named Silver Chariot.
Powers fast and precise swordmanship.
The honor is all mine.
Give me a break.
Excuse me, sir!
Huh?
I'm sorry, but could I bug you
to take our picture, maybe?
He's so hot!
What a good excuse to talk to him!
Please, will you do it?
I'll take it with the ocean behind us!
Shut up already!
Go bug someone else!
Easy, mon ami.
Ladies, I would love to
take your photograph.
Come along. There.
You have very nice legs.
I'll be sure to get them in the shot.
Ah!
Wee!
Perfection!
And another one for safety.
Très Bone,
if only I could use this camera to capture
your hearts instead of just your picture,
mademoiselle.
This is nothing like the
Polareff of a moment ago.
It's like his emotions change on a dime.
More like he's got two brains and the one
downstairs suddenly
started calling the shots.
Oh, give me a break.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino!
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They got their money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tight to the hookah, I say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian!
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian?
We're on a boat, kid!
Ditch the uniform already!
Even now, I'm a good student, Mr.
Joestar. Bring it on!
I'll take all you guys at once!
You're stand-disk.
Whenever one inhales any cigarette
smoke, the true nature is revealed.
By the way...